Narrator: A
A: Yes, I have. I drive a lot for my job, several hours a day,
and I like listening to books.
It’s much better than listening to the radio.
I probably listen to a couple of books every week.
Narrator: B
B: Yes, I’ve seen The Lord of the Rings movies at least four times.
They’re really great movies.
I never get tired of them, I always notice something new.
Narrator: C
C: Yes, I’ve definitely fallen asleep watching a movie on TV,
but never in the movie theater.
Narrator: D
D: Yes, I have.
I watched the complete fourth season of Stranger Things in one evening!
Narrator: E
E: No, I haven’t.
It usually takes me a long time to finish a book,
so I never read them again.
Narrator: F
F: Yes, I loved Encanto, you know, the Disney movie,
so I downloaded the soundtrack.
It’s got some great songs by a lot of different singers.